Guide to the Peter Gardner collection, 1959-1966 MS 779
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: KRBE - "The Sampler"
  - The Sampler - Sarah Wiggins, Guy Clark, Jerry Jeff Walker, 1966-01-24; 1966-01-26; Gardner_Sampler_41
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Sarah Wiggins - "Pretty Mary," "Lolly Too Dum"; Guy Clark - "Zebra Dun," "Tyin' a Knot in the Devil's Tail"; Guy Clark and Sarah Wiggins - "Keep Your Hands Off Her," "Early Morning Rain"; Jerry Jeff Walker - "New Orleans Talking Construction Blues"
  - The Sampler - Thomas H. Heiman, 1966-01-31; 1966-02-02; Gardner_Sampler_42
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Thomas H. Heiman - "Life Is a Little Sleep," "I Hide Behind a Name," "Making a Beginning," "There Is One," "Telescope Song," "Space Song for Children," "Sing Me the Moon," "Oh Bird," "I Saw a Funny Thing," "Something Strange," "We're Passing Yonder," "The Night of the Rose," "Make It and Break It," "Let's Get Together and Sing"
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Townes Van Zandt, Don Sanders, Guy Clark, 1966-02-07; 1966-02-09; Gardner_Sampler_43
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White - "Done Laid Around," "Comin' of the Roads," "High Flying Bird"; Townes Van Zandt - "Talkin' Karate Lesson Blues"; Townes Van Zandt and Gary White (harmonica) - "The Suicide Train" original; Townes Van Zandt - "Goodbye to an Old Friend"; Don Sanders - "Travelin' Man," "Bold Turpin," "What Did You Learn in School"; Guy Clark - "Golden Vanity," "Red Veltvet," "I Got Mine," "One Too Many Mornings," "Where I'm Bound," "Lesson Too Late for Learning"
  - The Sampler - Gary White, Susan Spaw, Amy Goodenough, Townes Van Zandt, Jerry Jeff Walker, 1966-02-14; 1966-02-23; Gardner_Sampler_44
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Gary White - "East Virginia," "Lady Gay," "Wild Goose Grasses," "Careless Love"; Susan Spaw - "I'm a Ramble," "Fare Thee Well," "Rest You Now"; Amy Goodenough - "Shiloh Town," "The Dove"; Townes Van Zandt - "Cocaine," "Thunderbird," "Just Waitin' around to Die" - wrote with wife and friend at a bar listing off all of the ways to die; Jerry Jeff Walker - "Be What You Want to Be," "It Had to Be," "Candy Man"; Gary White - "Birthday Song"
  - The Sampler - The Rumrunners, Sarah Wiggins, Frank Davis, Gary Boggs, David Boyce, Peter Childs, 1966-02-21; 1965-03-02; Gardner_Sampler_45
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. The Rumrunners - "Coal Tattoo," "Yesterday," "Early Morning Rain," "She Was Too Good to Me"; Sarah Wiggins - "Baby, Do You Hear Me," "Lonesome"; Frank Davis - "On a Monday," "Sweet Mary," "Rattlesnakes," "I'll Be So Glad," "Won't You Line Them," "Black Betty," "Jean Harlow"; Gary Boggs - "The Girl from Ipanema," "She Doesn't See"; David Boyce - "Scotch and Soda"; Peter Childs - "There By for Fortune," "Keep Your Hands off Her." The Rumrunners - musicians - David Boyce, Gary Boggs, Ray Rogers
  - The Sampler - Kathy Rote, Don Sanders, Carolyn Terry, Pete Wheeler, Amy Goodenough, Paul Johnson, 1966-02-28; 1966-03-09; Gardner_Sampler_46
    Contents include: Recorded live at 716 W. Alabama at Peter Gardner's home. Kathy Rote - "Fennario," "Lord Gregory," "Two Boys"; Don Sanders - "Portland County Jail," "My Rough and Rowdy Ways," "Brazos," "Andorra"; Carolyn Terry - "Shake Sugaree," "Sand Mountain Blues," "There Are Blues"; Pete Wheeler - "Merry Pirates Life," "High Barbary," "The Ninety and Nine"; Amy Goodenough - "New Shoes Blues," "Man Who Goes Away"; Amy Goodenough and Paul Johnson - "Single Girl"; Paul Johnson - "Danny Boy," "Girl from North Country"; Paul Johnson and Amy Goodenough - "Winken and Blinken and Nod"
  - The Sampler - Paul Johnson, Amy Goodenough, Gary White, Carolyn Terry, 1966-03-07; 1966-03-16; Gardner_Sampler_47
    Contents include: Recorded live at the home of Rick and Louise Ack. Paul Johnson and Amy Goodenough - "A Sailor's Life"; Gary White - "Trees They Grow High," "Alberta," "Go to Sea No More"; Paul Johnson - "Bye Bye My Baby"; Amy Goodenough - "Bury Me Not," "I Love My Baby"; Carolyn Terry - "Redwing Blackbird," "The Bold Fimian Man"; Gary White - "Freight Train," "Won't You Go down Hannah," "Run Come See," "Got a Home in That Rock"; Paul Johnson - "Sylvie"; Gary White - "Dark as a Dungeon," "Blowing in the Wind," "This Land"
  - The Sampler - Susan Spaw, Townes Van Zandt, Peter Gardner, Carolyn Terry, Gary White, 1966-03-14; 1966-03-23; Gardner_Sampler_48
    Contents include: Recorded live at the home of Rick and Louise Ack. Susan Spaw - "Can't Help But Wonder," "Come My Love," "Take Me Home with You" original song; Townes Van Zandt with Gary White on harmonica - "Bluebird Blues," "Don't Lie Lonesome," "Lonesome Feeling" [?] original, "Things I Don't Understand" [?] original, "Talking Karate Blues," "I'm Blue" [?] original, "Take My Body Home"; Peter Gardner and Gary White - "The Nightingale"; Peter Gardner - "Empty Pocket Blues"; Carolyn Terry - "Peter Emberly," "Ella Speed"; Gary White - "Mary Don't You Weep"